let questions = [
  {
    "numb": 51,
    "question": "A pest population is called uncontrolled when",
    "answer": "it is causing excessive economic damage",
    "options": ["it is increasing", "it is not decreasing", "it is causing some economic damage", "it is causing excessive economic damage"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 52,
    "question": "The impact of El Nino on fishery collapse in Peru is explained by",
    "answer": "match- mismatch hypothesis",
    "options": ["match hypothesis", "mismatch hypothesis", "match- mismatch hypothesis", "none of these"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 53,
    "question": "Which of these is correct",
    "answer": "R + G = M + F",
    "options": ["R + G = M + F", "R + M = G + F", "R + F + M + G", "R + G + M + F = 0"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 54,
    "question": "Ludwig's ratchet predicts",
    "answer": "increasing harvesting rate",
    "options": ["decreasing harvesting rate", "constant harvesting rate", "increasing harvesting rate", "fluctuating harvesting rate"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 55,
    "question": "A root zone treatment plant is an example of",
    "answer": "phytoremediation",
    "options": ["phytoremediation", "biological control", "biomagnification", "bioaccumulation"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 56,
    "question": "A pest population is called controlled when",
    "answer": "it is not causing excessive economic damage",
    "options": ["it is increasing", "it is decreasing", "it is not causing any economic damage", "it is not causing excessive economic damage"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 57,
    "question": "A deciduous forest in Madhya Pradesh was converted into a mine. After the mining operations were over, the pits were filled up with water and a lake was created. It is now visited by several migratory birds. This is an example of",
    "answer": "replacement",
    "options": ["recovery", "restoration", "enhancement", "replacement"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 58,
    "question": "A deciduous forest in Madhya Pradesh was converted into a mine. After the mining operations were over, the pits were filled up with soil and species of deciduous forest planted again. This is an example of",
    "answer": "restoration",
    "options": ["recovery", "restoration", "enhancement", "replacement"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 59,
    "question": "Which of these is not an impact of toxic chemicals",
    "answer": "reduction of existing stressors",
    "options": ["lethal effects", "sub-lethal effects", "reduction of existing stressors", "reduce fecundity"]
  },
  {
    "numb": 60,
    "question": "Which of these is correct",
    "answer": "the maximum sustainable yield is near the mid-point of the sigmoid curve",
    "options": ["the maximum sustainable yield is near the beginning of sigmoid curve", "the maximum sustainable yield is near the mid-point of sigmoid curve", "the maximum sustainable yield is near the end of sigmoid curve", "none of these"]
  }
]